Daniel Gizzi Díaz

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

I am a Computer Engineer with more than 4 years of experience as a Frontend Developer, focused on the development of friendly interfaces and a pleasant user experience. I have experience working in multidisciplinary teams and under agile methodologies. In addition, I have experience in different technologies such as, React, Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, SASS, Redux, HTML5, Git, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Entel

Front-End Developer

2023 - Present

- Develop reusable components, ensuring best practices, improving website performance and always focused on providing a good user experience.
- Support teammates in making decisions when a new development is to be carried out.
- Collaborate effectively with other teams such as Design, Backend and QA.
- Propose and implement new features to improve Entel's website.

Multiplica Talent

Front-End Developer 2022 -2023

- Develop reusable components, ensuring best practices, improving website performance and always focused on providing a good user experience.
- Support teammates in making decisions when a new development is to be carried out.
- Collaborate effectively with other teams such as Design, Backend and QA.
- Propose and implement new features to improve Entel's website.

O'Higgins University

Web Developer

2019 - 2022

- Planning and execution of promotional events to increase brand awareness.
- Collaboration with internal teams and external suppliers to ensure the successful execution of events.
- Evaluation of the effectiveness of activations by analyzing customer participation and feedback.

CONTACT



(56) 985083952



danielgizzidiaz@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/daniel-thomas-gizzi-diaz/

SKILLS

- React
- Git
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- TailwindCSS
- HTML5
- SASS
- Kanban
- Scrum
- Jira

EDUCATION

Informatic Engineer

INACAP 2020 -2021

Analyst Programmer

INACAP 2017 -2019

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- English (Intermediate)